(Stuart:)Of course it is. It's a little wrong
to say a tomato is a vegetable.
(Stuart:)It's very wrong to say
it's a suspension bridge.
(Stuart:)But returning to the original issue,
Dick Grayson became Nightwing.
(Stuart:)A superhero in his own right.
"Batman Two" has to be the second Robin,
Jason Todd.
"Has to be"? "Has to be"?
(Sheldon:)I hope you're being
deliberately provocative.
PENNY: I found the decaf.
- Oh, great.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, herbal tea for me, please.
Barkeep, Alexander me.
(Leonard:)How about those two?
No, they're eating peanuts.
With my allergies, one kiss
would put me in Cedars-Sinai for a week.
(Leonard:)What about the ones in the corner?
(Howard:)Possible. Very possible.
(Howard:)You want the one in the whiplash collar
or the one who keeps blinking?
- I think Blinky's cute.
- Done, sir.